Office of Educational Affairs, School of Medicine Records UA146
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- School of Medicine Syllabi, 1985 -- 2020; 1989 -- 2014; UA146.001; 36.0 Linear Feet; 18 Digital Object(s) 18 digital objects containing 192 files.; 3.33 Gigabytes Of the 18 digital objects in this series, 13 have extent information and comprise 4.37 GBs of data.
  - M'11 Renal Pathophysiology Syllabus Second Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00013 (Box 23)
  - Physical Diagnosis II Spring 2009 TUSM 2011, UA146.001.023.00014 (Box 23)
  - M'11 Cardiovascular Pathophysiology Syllabus Second Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00015 (Box 23)
  - M'11 Pulmonary Systemic Pathology Second Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00016 (Box 23)
  - M'11 Pulmonary Pathophysiology Syllabus Second Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00017 (Box 23)
  - M'11 Endocrine Pathophysiology Second Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00018 (Box 23)
  - M'11 Gastrointestinal Systemic Pathology Second Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00019 (Box 23)
  - M'11 Gastrointestinal Pathophysiology Syllabus Second Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00020 (Box 23)
  - M'12 General Pathology Syllabus First Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00021 (Box 23)
  - M'12 Physical Diagnosis I Syllabus First Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00022 (Box 23)
  - M'11 Breast and Pelvic Examination Second Year Fall Semester 2008, UA146.001.023.00023 (Box 23)
  - M'11 Population Medicine Syllabus Part 2 Second Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00024 (Box 23)
  - M'12 Human Growth and Development Syllabus First Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00025 (Box 23)
  - M'12 Medical Physiology Syllabus Volume I First Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00026 (Box 23)
  - M'12 Medical Physiology Syllabus Volume II First Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00027 (Box 23)
  - M'12 Medical Clinical Anatomy Syllabus First Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00028 (Box 23)
  - M'11 Cardiovascular Systemic Pathology Second Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.023.00029 (Box 23)
  - M'11 Reproductive Pathophysiology Second Year Spring Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - M'13 Epidemiology/Biostatistics Syllabus First Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - M'12 Population Medicine Syllabus Part 1 Second Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00003 (Box 24)
  - M'12 Psychopathology Syllabus Second Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00004 (Box 24)
  - M'12 Introduction to Pharmacology Syllabus 8/17/2009 - 8/28/2009 Second Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00005 (Box 24)
  - M'12 Medical Microbiology and Infectious Disease Syllabus Second Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00006 (Box 24)
  - M'12 Hematology/Oncology Syllabus Second Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00007 (Box 24)
  - M'13 Scientific Foundations of Medicine II Medical Clinical Anatomy Syllabus Part 1 Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00008 (Box 24)
  - M'13 Scientific Foundations of Medicine I Patient Presentations First Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00009 (Box 24)
  - M'13 Scientific Foundations of Social and Behavioral Medicine Syllabus Part 1 Spring Semester 2010, UA146.001.024.00010 (Box 24)
  - M'13 Scientific Foundations of Medicine I Syllabus Part IV Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00011 (Box 24)
  - M'12 Musculoskeletal Syllabus Second Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00012 (Box 24)
  - M'13 Ethics and Professionalism I Syllabus Part 1 First Year Academic Year 2009-2011, UA146.001.024.00013 (Box 24)
  - M'13 Scientific Foundations of Medicine II Syllabus Part II Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00014 (Box 24)
  - M'13 Scientific Foundations of Medicine II Syllabus Part III Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00015 (Box 24)
  - M'13 Foundations of Patient Care I Physical Diagnosis First Year Academic Year 2009-2010, UA146.001.024.00016 (Box 24)
  - M'12 Physical Diagnosis II Second Year Spring Semester 2010, UA146.001.024.00017 (Box 24)
  - M'12 Population Medicine Syllabus Part 2 Second Year Spring Semester 2010, UA146.001.024.00018 (Box 24)
  - M'12 Renal Syllabus Second Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00019 (Box 24)
  - M'12 Musculoskelatal Additional Lectures Syllabus Second Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00020 (Box 24)
  - M'13 Evidence-based Medicine Syllabus First Year Academic Year 2009-2010, UA146.001.024.00021 (Box 24)
  - M'13 Scientific Foundations of Medicine II Syllabus Part I Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.024.00022 (Box 24)
  - M'12 Physical Diagnosis II Breast and Pelvis Syllabus Second Year Spring Semester 2010, UA146.001.024.00023 (Box 24)
  - M'12 Pulmonary Syllabus Second Year Spring Semester 2010, UA146.001.024.00024 (Box 24)
  - M'13 The Brain Medical Clinical Anatomy Head and Neck Second Year Spring Semester 2010 Academic Year 2009-2010, UA146.001.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - M'13 The Brain Psychopathology Spring Semester 2010 Academic Year 2009-2010, UA146.001.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - M'12 Neuroscience Syllabus Second Year Fall Semester 2009 Academic Year 2009-2010, UA146.001.025.00003 (Box 25)
  - M'13 Foundations of Patient Care I Medical Interviewing and the Doctor-Patient Relationship Syllabus First Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.025.00004 (Box 25)
  - M'13 The Brain Addiction Medicine Spring Semester 2010, UA146.001.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - M'13 Scientific Foundations of Medicine I Syllabus Part II First Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.025.00006 (Box 25)
  - M'12 Cardiovascular Syllabus Second Year Spring Semester 2010, UA146.001.025.00007 (Box 25)
  - M'12 Addiction Medicine Syllabus Second Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.025.00008 (Box 25)
  - M'12 Medical Genetics Syllabus Second Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.025.00009 (Box 25)
  - M'13 Scientific Foundations of Medicine I Syllabus Part III Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.025.00010 (Box 25)
  - M'13 The Brain Neuroscience Spring Semester 2010, UA146.001.025.00011 (Box 25)
  - M'13 Foundations of Patient Care CAP 2010-2011, UA146.001.025.00012 (Box 25)
  - M'13 The Brain Neuroscience Lab Manual Spring Semester 2010, UA146.001.025.00013 (Box 25)
  - M'12 Gastrointestinal Syllabus Second Year Spring Semester 2010, UA146.001.025.00014 (Box 25)
  - M'12 Medical Microbiology and Infectious Disease Laboratory Manual Second Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.025.00015 (Box 25)
  - M'12 Endocrine Syllabus Second Year Spring Semester 2010, UA146.001.025.00016 (Box 25)
  - M'12 Reproductive Syllabus Second Year Spring Semester 2010, UA146.001.025.00017 (Box 25)
  - M'13 Scientific Foundations of Social and Behavioral Medicine Syllabus Part 2 Spring Semester 2010, UA146.001.025.00018 (Box 25)
  - M'13 Scientific Foundations of Medicine I Syllabus Part I First Year Fall Semester 2009, UA146.001.025.00019 (Box 25)
  - M'14 Introduction to Clinical Reasoning, Second Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00001 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Foundations of Patient Care, Competency-based Apprenticeship in Primary Care, 2011 -- 2012; UA146.001.026.00002 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Foundations of Patient Care, Competency-based Apprenticeship in Primary Care, Breast and Pelvis Syllabus, 2011; UA146.001.026.00003 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Health to Disease - Endocrinology, Second Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00004 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Health to Disease - Gastrointestinal, Second Year, 2012; UA146.001.026.00005 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Health to Disease - Reproductive, Second Year, 2012; UA146.001.026.00006 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Health to Disease III - Nutrition and Medicine, Second Year, 2012; UA146.001.026.00007 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Health to Disease - Dermatology, Second Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00008 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Health to Disease - Rheumatology, Second Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00009 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Health to Disease - Medical Microbiology & Infectious Disease Laboratory Manual, Second Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00010 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Health to Disease - Medical Microbiology & Infectious Disease, Second Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00011 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Health to Disease - Hematology/Oncology, Second Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00012 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Health to Disease - Cardiovascular, Second Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00013 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Health to Disease - Pulmonary, Second Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00014 (Box 26)
  - M'14 Health to Disease - Renal, Second Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00015 (Box 26)
  - M'15 Scientific Foundations of Medicine II Syllabus Part 1, 2011; UA146.001.026.00016 (Box 26)
  - M'15 Scientific Foundations of Medicine II Syllabus Part 2, 2011; UA146.001.026.00017 (Box 26)
  - M'15 Scientific Foundations of Medicine II Syllabus Part 3, 2011; UA146.001.026.00018 (Box 26)
  - M'15 Scientific Foundations of Medicine II Syllabus Part 4, 2012; UA146.001.026.00019 (Box 26)
  - Selective Program Catalog, 2011 -- 2012; UA146.001.026.00020 (Box 26)
  - M'15 Scientific Foundations of Medicine II Medical Clinical Anatomy, 2011; UA146.001.026.00021 (Box 26)
  - M'15 Scientific foundatiosn of Medicine I Patient Presentations, First Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00022 (Box 26)
  - M'15 Scientific Foundations of Medicine I Syllabus Part 1, First Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00023 (Box 26)
  - M'15 Scientific Foundations of Medicine I Syllabus Part 2, First Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00024 (Box 26)
  - M'15 Scientific Foundations of Medicine I Syllabus Part 3, First Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00025 (Box 26)
  - M'15 Scientific Foundations of Medicine I Syllabus Part 4, First Year, 2011; UA146.001.026.00026 (Box 26)
  - M'15 The Brain - Medical Clinical Anatomy Head and Neck, 2012; UA146.001.027.00001 (Box 27)
  - M'15 The Brain - Addiction Medicine, 2012; UA146.001.027.00002 (Box 27)
  - M'15 The Brain - Introduction to Clinical Psychiatry, 2012; UA146.001.027.00003 (Box 27)
  - M'15 The Brain - Neuroscience Lab Manual, 2012; UA146.001.027.00004 (Box 27)
  - M'15 The Brain - Neuroscience, 2012; UA146.001.027.00005 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Foundations of Evidence-Based Medicine and Clinical Reasoning - Epidemiology/Biostatistics, First Year, 2011; UA146.001.027.00006 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Foundations of Patient Care - Competency-based Apprenticeship in Primary Care, 2012 -- 2013; UA146.001.027.00007 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Foundations of Patient Care I - Physical Diagnosis, First Year, 2011 -- 2012; UA146.001.027.00008 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Foundations of Patient Care I - Medical Interviewing the Doctor - Patient Relationship, First Year, 2011; UA146.001.027.00009 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Evidence-Based Medicine, First Year, 2011 -- 2012; UA146.001.027.00010
  - M'15 Principles of Medical Ethics & Professionalism, First Year, 2011 -- 2012; UA146.001.027.00011
  - M'15 To Finish Working On, First Year, 2011 -- 2012; UA146.001.027.00012
  - M'15 Health to Disease Pulmonary - Second Year, 2012; UA146.001.027.00013 (Box 27)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - M'15 Health to Disease Renal - Second Year, 2012; UA146.001.027.00014 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Health to Disease Cardiovascular - Second Year, 2012; UA146.001.027.00015 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Health to Disease Hematology/Oncology - Second Year 1 of 2, 2012; UA146.001.027.00016 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Health to Disease Hematology/Oncology - Second Year 2 of 2, 2012; UA146.001.027.00017 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Health to Disease Dermatology - Second Year, 2012; UA146.001.027.00018 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Health to Disease Rheumatology - Second Year, 2012; UA146.001.027.00019 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Health to Disease Medical Microbiology and Infectious Disease - Second Year, 2012; UA146.001.027.00021 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Health to Disease Medical Microbiology and Infectious Disease Lab Manual- Second Year, 2012; UA146.001.027.00022 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Health to Disease Gastrointestinal - Second Year, 2013; UA146.001.027.00023 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Health to Disease Nutrition and Medicine - Second Year, 2013; UA146.001.027.00024 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Health to Disease Endocrinology - Second Year, 2013; UA146.001.027.00025 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Health to Disease Reproductive - Second Year, 2013; UA146.001.027.00026 (Box 27)
  - M'15 CAP I, 2012 -- 2013; UA146.001.027.00027 (Box 27)
    Competency-based Aprrenticeship in Primary Care - Used over the course of two years
  - M'15 CAP II: Breast and Pelvic - Second Year, 2012; UA146.001.027.00028 (Box 27)
    Addition to CAP I Syllabus
  - M'15 Introduction to Clinical Reasoning - Second Year, 2012; UA146.001.027.00029 (Box 27)
  - M'15 Ethics and Professionalism II, 2013; UA146.001.027.00030
  - M'16 Patient Presentations - First Year, 2012; UA146.001.027.00031 (Box 27)
  - M'16 Medfoundations 1 Part 1: Biochemistry, Medical Genetics, and Medical Cell Biology - First Year, 2012; UA146.001.027.00032 (Box 27)
  - M'16 Medfoundations 1 Part 2: Biochemistry Part II, Genetics Part II, Cell Biology Part II, and Tissue and Organ Biology Part I - First Year, 2012; UA146.001.027.00033 (Box 27)
  - M'16 Medfoundations 1 Part 3: Biochemistry Part III, Tissue and Organ Biology Part II, Immunology Part 1, Introduction to Microbiology: A Molecular Approach Part I - First Year, 2012; UA146.001.028.00001 (Box 28)
    Additional room in box to add more and send off-site
  - M'16 Medfoundations 1 Part 4: Biochemistry Part IV, Tissue and Organ Biology Part III, Immunology Part II, Introduction to Microbiology: A Molecular Approach Part II - First Year, 2012; UA146.001.028.00002 (Box 28)
  - M'16 Epidemiology/Biostatistics - First Year, 2012; UA146.001.028.00003 (Box 28)
  - M'16 Medical Interviewing and the Doctor - Patient Relationship - First Year, 2012; UA146.001.028.00004 (Box 28)
  - Selective Program Catalog, 2012 -- 2013; UA146.001.028.00006 (Box 28)
  - M'16 Medfoundations II Part 1: Core Physiology Part I, Cort Pathology Part I, Core Pharmacology Part I - First Year, 2012; UA146.001.028.00007 (Box 28)
  - M'16 Clinical Anatomy, 2012; UA146.001.028.00008 (Box 28)
    Taught during Medfoundations II
  - M'16 Physical Diagnosis I, 2012 -- 2013; UA146.001.028.00009 (Box 28)
    Taught during Medfoundations II and The Brain Unit
  - M'16 Medfoundations II Part 2: Core Physiology Part II, Core Pathology Part II, 2013; UA146.001.028.00010 (Box 28)
  - M'16 Medfoundations II Part 3: Core Physiology Part III, 2013; UA146.001.028.00011 (Box 28)
  - M'16 Neuroscience, 2013; UA146.001.028.00012 (Box 28)
    Taught during the Brain Unit
  - M'16 Introduction to Clinical Psychiatry, 2013; UA146.001.028.00013 (Box 28)
  - M'16 Head and Neck Anatomy, 2013; UA146.001.028.00014 (Box 28)
  - M'16 Addiction Medicine, 2013; UA146.001.028.00015 (Box 28)
  - M'16 CAP I - First Year, 2013 -- 2014; UA146.001.028.00018 (Box 28)
    Competency-based Apprenticeship in Primary Care
  - Evidence Base Medicine Boston Syllabus, 2013; UA146.001.028.00019
  - M'17- Scientific Foundations of Medicine I, Syllabus Part I, 2013 -- 2014; UA146.001.041.00001 (Box 41)
  - M'17- Scientific Foundations of Medicine I, Syllabus Part II, 2013 -- 2014; UA146.001.041.00002 (Box 41)
  - M'17- Scientific Foundations of Medicine I, Syllabus Part III, 2013 -- 2014; UA146.001.041.00003 (Box 41)
  - M'17- Scientific Foundations of Medicine I, Syllabus Part IV, 2013 -- 2014; UA146.001.041.00004 (Box 41)
  - M'17- Foundations of Evidence-Based Medicine and Clinical Reasoning Syllabus, 2013 -- 2014; UA146.001.041.00005 (Box 41)
  - M'17- Foundations of Patient Care I, 2013; UA146.001.041.00006 (Box 41)
  - Selective Program Catalog, 2013 -- 2014; UA146.001.041.00007 (Box 41)
  - M'17- Physical Diagnosis I Syllabus, 2013 -- 2014; UA146.001.041.00008 (Box 41)
  - M'17- Scientific Foundations of Medicine II Syllabus Part I, 2013; UA146.001.041.00009 (Box 41)
  - M'17- Scientific Foundations of Medicine II Syllabus Part II, 2013; UA146.001.041.00010 (Box 41)
  - M'17- Scientific Foundations of Medicine II Syllabus Part III, 2013; UA146.001.041.00011 (Box 41)
  - M'17- Scientific Foundations of Medicine II Syllabus Part IV, 2014; UA146.001.041.00012 (Box 41)
  - M'17- Scientific Foundations of Medicine II, Medical Clinical Anatomy Syllabus, 2013; UA146.001.041.00013 (Box 41)
  - M'17- The Brain, Neuroscience, 2014; UA146.001.041.00014 (Box 41)
  - M'17- The Brain, Intro to Clinical Psychiatry, 2014; UA146.001.041.00015 (Box 41)
  - M'17- The Brain, Medical Clinical Anatomy, Head and Neck, 2014; UA146.001.041.00016 (Box 41)
  - M'17- The Brain, Addiction Medicine Syllabus, 2014; UA146.001.041.00017 (Box 41)
  - M'17- Foundations of Patient Care, 2014 -- 2015; UA146.001.041.00018 (Box 41)
  - M'16- Health to Disease, Pulmonary Syllabus, 2013; UA146.001.041.00019 (Box 41)
  - M'16- Health to Disease, Renal Syllabus, 2013; UA146.001.041.00020 (Box 41)
  - M'16- Health to Disease, Cardiovascular Syllabus, 2013; UA146.001.041.00021 (Box 41)
  - M'16- Health to Disease, Hematology/Oncology Syllabus, 2013; UA146.001.042.00001 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - M'16- Health to Disease, Dermatology Syllabus, 2013; UA146.001.042.00002 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - M'16- Health to Disease, Rheumatology Syllabus, 2013; UA146.001.042.00003 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - M'16- Health to Disease, Medical Microbiology ande Infectious Disease Syllabus, 2013; UA146.001.042.00004 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - M'16- Health to Disease, Medical Microbiology ande Infectious Disease Lab Manuel, 2013; UA146.001.042.00005 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - M'16- Health to Disease, Gastrointestinal Syllabus, 2014; UA146.001.042.00006 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - M'16- Health to Disease, Nutrition and Medicine Syllabus, 2014; UA146.001.042.00007 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - M'16- Health to Disease, Endocrinology Syllabus, 2014; UA146.001.042.00008 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - M'16- Health to Disease, reproductive Syllabus, 2014; UA146.001.042.00009 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - M'16- Foundations of Patient Care Cap, 2013 -- 2014; UA146.001.042.00010 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - 2013 All Students SFSBM Syllabus, UA146.001.042.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 59.93 Megabytes
    2013 All Students SFSBM Syllabus
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by the Office of Educational Affairs of the School of Medicine, 2016, accession 2017.027.
  - 2013 Ethics 2 Syllabus, UA146.001.042.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.85 Megabytes
    2013 Ethics 2 Syllabus
  - 2013 Ethics I Syllabus, UA146.001.042.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 45.52 Megabytes
    2013 Ethics I Syllabus
  - 2013 Maine EBM Syllabus, UA146.001.042.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.22 Megabytes
    2013 Maine EBM Syllabus
  - EBM 2013 Boston Syllabus, UA146.001.042.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.65 Megabytes
    EBM 2013 Boston Syllabus
  - M19 Second Year Syllabi, 2016 -- 2017; UA146.001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s) One digital object comprising 16 files.; 220.3 Megabytes
  - M20 First Year Syllabi, 2016 -- 2017; UA146.001.00002; 1 Digital Object(s) One digital object comprising 23 files.; 790.3 Megabytes
  - M20 Second Year Syllabi, 2017 -- 2018; UA146.001.00003; 1 Digital Object(s) One digital object comprising 17 files.; 209.8 Megabytes
  - M21 First Year Syllabi, 2017 -- 2018; UA146.001.00004; 1 Digital Object(s) One digital object comprising 25 files.; 693.5 Megabytes
  - M21 Second Year Syllabi, 2018 -- 2019; UA146.001383; 398 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) One digital object comprising 17 files.
  - M22 First Year Syllabi, 2018 -- 2019; UA146.001384; 905 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) One digital object comprising 26 files.
  - M22 Second Year Syllabi, 2019 -- 2020; UA146.001385; 1 Digital Object(s) One digital object comprising 26 files.; 473 Megabytes
  - M23 First Year Syllabi, 2019 -- 2020; UA146.001386; 1 Digital Object(s) One digital object comprising 32 files.; 571 Megabytes
- Additional accessions, UA146.002; 4 Digital Object(s)
  - IGC grant, 1994; UA146-019
    A word file which includes a to-do list, draft letter of support, and partial draft of grant. This item was originally located in UA146.004.030.00003.
  - Making Care Decisions at the End of Life, UA146-020
    This digital object was a set of three CD-ROMS that were transferred using BagIt in 2014-05 by Dan Bullman.
  - First year syllabi, 2014 -- 2015; UA146-021 (Box data_value_missing_6bc5c2eed526785ec1ed5c9a68acda19, Box 1)
  - Second year syllabi, 2014 -- 2015; UA146-022 (Box data_value_missing_f6e2dc15e2b90a6c0f557c4cc3049c82, Box 2)
  - Syllabi, 2013 -- 2015; UA146-023
  - Syllabi, 2015 -- 2016; UA146-024
- School of Medicine class schedules and committee minutes, 1968 -- 2009; UA146.003; 6.0 Linear Feet
  75 years from the date of creation. 20 years from date of creation.
  - 1st Year Spring, 1980 -- 1981; UA146.003.036.00001 (Box 36)
  - Class of 1986, First year, Second Trimester, UA146.003.036.00002 (Box 36)
  - 1st Year Fall, 1982; UA146.003.036.00003 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Units C,D, E, 1983; UA146.003.036.00004 (Box 36)
  - 1st Year Fall, 1983; UA146.003.036.00005 (Box 36)
  - Schedules/Course Assignments, 1973 -- 1975; UA146.003.036.00006 (Box 36)
  - 1st Year Fall, 1977; UA146.003.036.00007 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Units A & B, 1983; UA146.003.036.00008 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Units A & B, 1983 -- 1984; UA146.003.036.00009 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Units C, D, E, 1982; UA146.003.036.00010 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Units A & B, 1982 -- 1983; UA146.003.036.00011 (Box 36)
  - 1st year Spring, 1982; UA146.003.036.00012 (Box 36)
  - 1st year Spring, 1979; UA146.003.036.00013 (Box 36)
  - Renal Systems Curriculum, 1980; UA146.003.036.00014 (Box 36)
  - 1st Year Fall, 1981; UA146.003.036.00015 (Box 36)
  - Cardiovascular System, 1977; UA146.003.036.00016 (Box 36)
  - 1st year Fall, 1980; UA146.003.036.00017 (Box 36)
  - Course Evaluation Reports, 2004; UA146.003.036.00018 (Box 36)
  - Curriculum Committee, 2003 -- 2004; UA146.003.036.00019 (Box 36)
  - Curriculum Committee Meetings, 2003 -- 2004; UA146.003.036.00020 (Box 36)
  - Curriculum Committee Meetings, 2002; UA146.003.036.00021 (Box 36)
  - Currciulum Committee, 2002; UA146.003.036.00022 (Box 36)
  - Currciulum Committee, 2002; UA146.003.036.00023 (Box 36)
  - Currciulum Committee, 2002; UA146.003.036.00024 (Box 36)
  - Currciulum Committee, 2002; UA146.003.036.00025 (Box 36)
  - Nutrition and Medicine, 2003; UA146.003.036.00026 (Box 36)
  - Currciulum Committee, 2003; UA146.003.036.00027 (Box 36)
  - Currciulum Committee, 2003; UA146.003.036.00028 (Box 36)
  - Currciulum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.036.00029 (Box 36)
  - Currciculum Plan Committee, 1993; UA146.003.036.00030 (Box 36)
  - Currciculum Plan Committee, 1996; UA146.003.036.00031 (Box 36)
  - Curriculum Planning, 1995; UA146.003.036.00032 (Box 36)
  - Planning Group for Curriculum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.036.00033 (Box 36)
  - Planning Group for Curriculum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.036.00034 (Box 36)
  - Planning Group for Curriculum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.036.00035 (Box 36)
  - Planning Group for Curriculum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.036.00036 (Box 36)
  - Planning Group for Curriculum Committee, 1997; UA146.003.036.00037 (Box 36)
  - Curriculum Committee Meeting, 1991; UA146.003.036.00038 (Box 36)
  - Currciulum Committee, 1988; UA146.003.036.00039 (Box 36)
  - Planning Group for Curriculum Committee, 1997; UA146.003.036.00040 (Box 36)
  - Planning Group for Curriculum Committee, 1997; UA146.003.036.00041 (Box 36)
  - Planning Group for Curriculum Committee, 1997; UA146.003.036.00042 (Box 36)
  - Planning Group for Curriculum Committee, 1997; UA146.003.036.00043 (Box 36)
  - First Year, First Trimester, 1974 -- 1975; UA146.003.036.00044 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year Systems, Physical Diagnosis, 1980 -- 1981; UA146.003.036.00045 (Box 36)
  - 1st Year Spring, 1983; UA146.003.036.00046 (Box 36)
  - Handouts, CC Mtgs, 1995; UA146.003.036.00047 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Units C,D, E, 1984; UA146.003.036.00048 (Box 36)
  - Course Schedules, 1977 -- 1979; UA146.003.036.00049 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year Systems, Renal, 1979; UA146.003.036.00050 (Box 36)
  - 1st year- Fall 1979, UA146.003.036.00051 (Box 36)
  - 1st year fall, 1984; UA146.003.036.00052 (Box 36)